Sleep has gone from being a sleepy topic to one that is now heavily studied by top-tier researchers.
睡眠は、かつては地味なテーマとされていましたが、今や一流の研究者たちが熱心に研究する分野となっています。
While there is still some mystery surrounding why humans need so much sleep,
人間がなぜこれほど多くの睡眠を必要とするのか、その理由にはまだいくつかの謎が残っていますが、
there really is no mystery about how essential it is to get enough.
十分な睡眠をとることがいかに重要であるかについては、もはや疑う余地がありません。
Yet, when I talk with my clients and ask them how they're sleeping,
しかし、私がクライアントと話して「最近、睡眠はどうですか？」と尋ねると、
about half of the time I'm met with, I roll size and visible frustration.
およそ半数の方々が、ため息をついたり、明らかにイライラした表情を見せます。
Many people simply aren't sleeping well.
多くの人が、単純に十分に眠れていないのです。
Hi, I'm Melanie Luther, I'm a certified nutrition specialist and a licensed dietitian nutritionist.
こんにちは、私はメラニー・ルーサー（Melanie Luther）です。認定栄養スペシャリストであり、免許を持つ管理栄養士でもあります。
Level up your sleep is a thoughtfully designed nutritional supplement that may help support better sleep.
『レベルアップ・ユア・スリープ（Level Up Your Sleep）』は、より良い睡眠をサポートするために慎重に設計された栄養補助食品です。
It contains magnesium by glycinate, a highly bio-available, well absorbed form of this essential mineral.
このサプリメントには、キレート型マグネシウム（マグネシウム・バイグリシン酸塩）が含まれており、この必須ミネラルの非常に吸収されやすく生体利用率の高い形態です。
Research suggests that magnesium by glycinate may modestly improve sleep quality
研究によると、キレート型マグネシウムは睡眠の質をわずかではあるものの有意に改善し、
and support both falling asleep and staying asleep.
入眠および睡眠維持をサポートする可能性があります。
Without adequate magnesium, it's incredibly difficult for the nervous system to relax and turn off at night.
十分なマグネシウムがなければ、夜間に神経系をリラックスさせ、活動をオフにすることは極めて困難です。
L-fianian is a non-essential amino acid that helps to ease the mind.
L-テアニン（L-theanine）は非必須アミノ酸の一種で、心を落ち着けるのに役立ちます。
It supports the transition from the active brain wave states of alertness and problem solving
これは、覚醒時や問題解決時に見られる活発な脳波状態から、
into the alpha state associated with relaxation and meditation.
リラックスや瞑想に関連するアルファ波の状態への移行をサポートします。
A state much more conducive for sleeping.
この状態は、睡眠にとってはるかに適しています。
Many people find it helps you quiet that mental chatter that seems to get louder
多くの人が、枕に頭を置いた瞬間に急に大きくなるような
the moment our heads hit the pillow.
頭の中の雑念を静めるのに役立つと感じています。
Ashragand is another valuable addition to this formula.
アシュワガンダ（Ashwagandha）もこの処方に加えられたもう一つの貴重な成分です。
A meta-analysis of five randomized controlled trials involving over 400 participants
400人以上の参加者を対象とした5つの無作為化比較試験を統合したメタ分析では、
found a small but significant improvement in overall sleep with the greatest benefit seen
全体的な睡眠のわずかだが有意な改善が認められ、特に不眠症を抱える人々において
in individuals experiencing insomnia.
最も大きな効果が得られました。
Its angelitic properties, meaning it's ability to calm feelings of anxiety, may also
また、アシュワガンダには抗不安作用（不安感を和らげる働き）があり、
support sleep in those experiencing chronic stress.
慢性的なストレスを抱える人の睡眠をサポートする可能性もあります。
Last but not least is Vitamin B6.
最後に忘れてはならないのが、ビタミンB6です。
This essential B vitamin is required for the production of key sleep-related neurotransmitters,
この必須ビタミンB群の一つは、メラトニン、GABA、セロトニン、ドーパミンなど、
including melatonin, GABA, serotonin and dopamine.
睡眠に関与する主要な神経伝達物質の生成に不可欠です。
It's also important to know that regular alcohol consumption and high caffeine intake
また、日常的なアルコール摂取やカフェインの過剰摂取は、
can negatively impact vitamin B6 status which may contribute to difficulty falling or staying
ビタミンB6の体内濃度に悪影響を及ぼし、入眠や睡眠維持の困難さの一因となる
asleep.
可能性があることも知っておくべきです。
Additionally, I think it's important to know that supplementing with Vitamin B6 may increase
さらに、ビタミンB6をサプリメントとして摂取すると、
dream vividness and recall.
夢の鮮明さや夢の記憶が増す可能性があることも重要です。
Thank you so much.
どうもありがとうございました。